jehzlau-concepts.com 2013-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Jehzlau Concepts

This statement discloses the privacy practices of Jehzlau Concepts.

At [Jehzlau Concepts](http://www.jehzlau-concepts.com/), I intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. In general, you can visit Jehzlau Concepts on the web without telling me who you are or revealing any information about yourself. I do however keep track of information that is not personally identifiable, such as the domains from which people visit me. This information is analyzed for trends and statistical purposes. There are also times when I may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before I collect personal information from you on the Internet.

If you choose to give me your personal information via the Internet that I or our business partners may need — to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example — it is our intent to let you know how I will use such information. If you tell me that you do not wish to have this personal information used as a basis for further contact with you, I will respect your wishes. I do keep track of the domains from which people visit this blog.

It is my goal to protect and secure the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. I have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is secure, accurate, current and complete. I will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.

**What information do I gather?**  
Information on Jehzlau Concepts are gathered in two ways: (1) indirectly (for example, through our site’s [technology](http://www.jehzlau-concepts.com/category/technology "technology")); and (2) directly (for example, when you provide information on various pages of Jehzlau Concepts).

One example of information I collect indirectly is through our Internet access logs. When you access Jehzlau Concepts, your Internet address is automatically collected and is placed in our Internet access logs.

I collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which I describe in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to Jehzlau Concepts—for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you. The cookies I use identify you merely as a number. (If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser.)

I also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to me. Throughout our site, I provide the opportunity to register for an event or conference, order a white paper, or participate in an online survey. When I collect this type of information, I will notify you as to why I are asking for information and how this information will be used. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

**How do I use this information?**  
I analyze it to determine what is most effective about our site, to help me identify ways to improve it, and eventually, to determine how I can tailor Jehzlau Concepts to make it more effective. I may also use data for other purposes, which I would describe to you at the point I collect the information.

**Will I share this with outside parties?**  
As a global organization, data I collect may be transferred internationally throughout Jehzlau Concepts’s worldwide organization. I will not sell individual information and will share it only with our advisors. There will be other times when I need to share information, for example, in the case of an event where I need to provide our caterer with meal preference information. But again, before you submit any information, I will notify you as to why I are asking for specific information and it is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

**What about sensitive personal data?**  
I do not generally seek to collect sensitive personal data through this site. If I do seek to collect such data, I will ask you to consent to our proposed uses of the data. I may also collect some sensitive personal data incidentally. By providing me with unsolicited sensitive personal data, you consent to our using the data subject to applicable law as described in this Privacy Statement. The references to “sensitive personal data” are to the various categories of personal data identified by European and other data privacy laws as requiring special treatment, including in some circumstances the need to obtain explicit consent. These categories comprise personal identity numbers, personal data about personality and private life, racial or ethnic origin, nationality, political opinions, membership of political parties or movements, religious, philosophical or other similar beliefs, membership of a trade union or profession or trade association, physical or mental health, genetic code, addictions, sexual life, property matters or criminal record (including information about suspected criminal activities).

**How About Your Advertisers?**  
I use third party advertisements such as [Google](http://www.jehzlau-concepts.com/category/all-about-google "Google") Adsense, BlogBank, Bidvertiser, and Widgetbucks. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and I do not have access to these information. You may check their websites for respective privacy policies.

Google Internet-based Ads Policy Updates:  
\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
\- Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**Do I give you access to your information?**  
You are entitled to know whether I hold information about you and, if I do, to have access to that information and require it to be corrected if it is inaccurate. You can do this by sending me an e-mail at jehzlau@dostscholars.org

**What about data security?**  
I take appropriate steps to maintain the security of your data on Jehzlau Concepts. You should understand that the open nature of the Internet is such that data may flow over networks without security measures and may be accessed and used by people other than those for whom the data is intended.

That’s it in a nutshell. The short of it is I am interested in maintaining your privacy and creating a valuable resource for you to use. If you have any questions now or during your visit, please contact me by sending me an SMS at 09105555515 or via e-mail: jehzlau@dostscholars.org.
